torbit.com 2016-05-31

# Torbit - Legal notices

## Protecting your privacy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Torbit collects, uses, maintains and discloses your information while visiting the Torbit website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Torbit. 

**Personal identification information**  
Torbit may collect personal identification information from you in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you browse our site, register on our Site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. You may be asked for, as appropriate, your name, email address, phone number and domain information. Of course, you may also visit our Site anonymously. Torbit will collect personal identification information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. You can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent you from engaging in certain Site related activities. 

**Non-personal identification information**  
Torbit may collect non-personal identification information about you whenever you interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about you means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. 

**Torbit browser cookies**  
Torbit may use "cookies" to enhance your experience. Your browser may places cookies on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about you. You may choose to set your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. 

**How Torbit uses collected information**   
Torbit collects and uses your personal information for the following purposes: 

a) To personalize your experience   
b) To share requested information about Torbit’s service   
c) To improve our Site using information in the aggregate to understand how our visitors use our services and resources provided on our Site.

We continually strive to improve our offering based on the information and feedback we receive from you. The email address you provide will only be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email we send. 

**How we protect your information**   
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. 

Sensitive and private data exchanged between our Site and your browser happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. 

**Sharing your personal information**   
Torbit will not sell, trade, or rent your personal identification information to others. Torbit may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding our visitors with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. Torbit may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. Torbit may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission. 

**Third party sites**   
You may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. Torbit does not control the content or links that appear on these sites and is not responsible for the practices employed by sites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. 

**Changes to this privacy policy**   
Torbit has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage you to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect your personal information. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

**Your acceptance of these terms**   
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

**Contacting Torbit**   
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with Torbit, please contact us. 

This document was last updated on April 10, 2012
